https://www.nycballet.com/footer-navigation/privacy-policy/

Unfortunately, it looks like you are using an outdated browser.
To improve your experience on our site and ensure your security, please upgrade to a modern browser such as Chrome, Firefox, Safari, or Edge.
Movement Workshops for Children with Physical Disabilities
Movement Workshops for Teens and Adults with Physical Disabilities
Movement Workshops for Children with Physical Disabilities
Movement Workshops for Teens and Adults with Physical Disabilities
Remove
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to nycballet.com and New York City Ballet and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to New York City Ballet include nycballet.com and NYCB. The NYCB website is an ecommerce and information site. By using the NYCB website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationIf you create an account on the NYCB site, NYCB may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name or email. If you purchase NYCB's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.If you make a purchase or donation by letter, phone, or in person, information about that transaction will also be collected. If you contact us by email, letter, phone, or in person, that information about the communication will also collected.Collection of Anonymous InformationInformation about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NYCB. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NYCB website.Links and Embedded ContentNYCB's website may include links to other sites or embedded content, such as our videos, which are hosted by Vimeo. Once you leave our servers, NYCB does not control the privacy policies of destination sites. NYCB encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from NYCB so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. NYCB is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the NYCB website.Use of Your Personal InformationNYCB collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.NYCB may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NYCB and its affiliates. NYCB may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.NYCB will never share, sell, rent or trade your personal information to any third parties for marketing purposes without your consent. We may occasionally share users’ names and postal addresses (but not email addresses) with like-minded, carefully selected nonprofit organizations. If you do not want your address exchanged in this way, please visit your My Account page to update your preferences, or email customercare@nycballet.com to ask that your name and address be removed from any shared mailing lists.We may combine information you have given to us with this additional information available from external sources. This will only be done when you give permission to the relevant third party organizations to share the data they hold on you, or if the data is already publicly available.NYCB may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NYCB, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.NYCB may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within NYCB, in order to determine what NYCB services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within NYCB to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.You may access, correct, amend, or delete the information we have about you by logging into your account and navigating to the My Account page. If you wish for us to remove your account from our database, please email customercare@nycballet.com with your request. If you do, personally identifiable information associated with your account will be deleted as soon as is reasonably practical or as required by applicable law. Please note that we may retain information that is otherwise deleted in anonymized and aggregated form, in archived or backup copies as required pursuant to records retention obligations, or otherwise as required by law.NYCB will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NYCB or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NYCB; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NYCB, or the public.Data HygieneFrom time to time we may screen our database against recognized data hygiene file such as National Change of Address file and cleanse our file or correct inaccurate data. We may also update inaccurate data if the information is available.Social MediaDepending on your settings or the privacy policies for social media and messaging services like Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp, YouTube, Vimeo, or Twitter, you may give us permission to access information from those accounts or services.Contest SponsorsNYCB may occasionally present a special contest or promotion that is sponsored by a third party. To qualify for entry, we may ask you to provide personal information. If NYCB plans to share the personal information requested from you with such sponsor(s), we will notify you on the webpage or in the correspondences through which this information is collected.Use of CookiesThe NYCB website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you. You can easily control and disable cookies through your browser settings.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NYCB pages, or register with NYCB site or services, a cookie helps NYCB to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NYCB website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NYCB features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NYCB services or websites you visit.Certain tracking technologies we use are related to advertising networks and through those technologies we may share certain information such as IP addresses. No personally identifiable information is shared with these advertising networks; please note that the information we share with those advertising networks might be combined with other information about you that those networks may have collected from other sources.To learn more about advertising networks and how to opt out of sharing information with them, please click here and here. If you’re in the EU, you can find additional information about your choices with respect to advertising networks and online behavioral advertising by clicking here.Security of Your Personal InformationWhen personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.Digicert is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust and provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the My Account page.Children Under ThirteenNYCB does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.Opt-Out & UnsubscribeWe respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from NYCB by contacting us here:My Account
customercare@nycballet.com
212-496-0600
Jurisdiction and VenueAll users, including those who access the web sites from a country other than the U.S., agree by virtue of their use that the laws of the State of New York shall govern any disputes, including any arising from or in connection with use of the sites and any arising from NYCB's use of personal information or otherwise relating to privacy and that any claim made against the NYCB can only be brought in a federal or state court in New York County, New York.Changes to this StatementNYCB will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. NYCB encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NYCB is protecting your information. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.Contact InformationNYCB welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NYCB has not adhered to this Statement, please contact NYCB at:New York City Ballet20 Lincoln Center Plz.New York, New York 10023Email Address: info@nycballet.comTelephone number: 212-496-0600Effective as of May 25, 2018
